question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Peter Molyneux was the founder of Bullfrog Productions.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan &quot;We hire mercenaries and get in fights&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, the clouds and bushes have the same artwork and are just different colors.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The game &quot;Pocket Morty&quot; has a Morty called &quot;Pocket Mortys Morty&quot;?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
